Marwa Mohammed Elsayed

- Abrag El-Mashtal, Assiut, Egypt (GMT+2)
- **J** +20 101 324 2637
- **™** marwa.mohamed8712000@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/marwa-mohammed-10330817b/

Summary

Hello there, My name is Marwa Mohammed, I'm a Frontend Web Developer 1 year in Information Technology Institute of team work experience and open source contributions.

In this duration, I have learned a lot of technologies, created many cool websites, collaborated with great developers.

So I'm always seeking to have an opportunity that matches my skills, to make the best use of all what I have learned.

Skills

- > HTML5
- JavaScript (ESNext)
- > JQuery
- > Git & Github
- > MySQL
- > C#

- > CSS3
- > JSON
- ➤ Bootstrap
- > Responsive Design
- > Database
- > Python

Languages

- > Arabic native
- > English conversational
- > French basic

Experience

> Virtual Internship - Web application using Laravel & PHP

Information Technology Institute

14 September 2022 - 18 November 2022

> MySQL Training

Petra Software - On-site July 2022 - Aug 2022

> ICPC Training

International Collegiate Programming Contest Aug 2020

Education

> Full-Stack Web Developer - Internship (9-Months)
Information Technology Institute - On-site
September 2022 - Present

> Bachelor of Computers and Information - Bioinformatics Department - Grade: Very Good & Graduation Project with Grade: Excellent Assiut university - Assiut - Egypt, Graduate, 2018 - 2022

Projects

> Multiple Sequence Alignment website

DNA Analysis in Biological Database (2021).

- Built with Python, PyCharm, ClustalW, and Streamlit Framework
- > Library Management System

Desktop application that aims to develop a computerized system to maintain all the daily work of a library (2019).

- Built with OOP, Java, GUI, and NetBeans
- > Garden Blog website (ITI)
- Built with Laravel, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, and Xampp

Community Activities

> Social media member

International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) - 2020

> Voice Over actor

Triple Bond Community - 2021

Certificates

- > Sololearn Responsive Web Design
- Verify at https://www.sololearn.com/certificates/CT-9R0WESUR
- > Sololearn Game Development with JavaScript
- Verify at https://www.sololearn.com/certificates/CT-JXMKZPGI
- > Sololearn HTML
- Verify at https://www.sololearn.com/certificates/CT-AXPGDC1X
- > Sololearn CSS
- Verify at https://www.sololearn.com/certificates/CT-DH3LRV81
- > Sololearn C++
- Verify at https://www.sololearn.com/certificates/CT-ERCNDNMM